[
  {
    "question": "(3 + a) * 5 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["15+5a", "5a+15"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a/7) * (2/b) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["2a/(7b)", "(2a)/(7b)"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "3/5 + 2/7 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["31/35"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "c * (5 - a) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["5c-ac", "5c - ac", "-ac+5c"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 : 4 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["0"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "number"
  },
  {
    "question": "3/5 : 7/2 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["6/35"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + b) : c =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["(a+b)/c", "a/c + b/c"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3 * a) * b =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["3ab"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 : 0 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["nem értelmezett", "0-val nem osztunk", "nincs értelmezve", "hiba"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a/b) : (2/7) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["7a/(2b)", "(7a)/(2b)", "7a/2b"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3a) * 5 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["-15a"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c * b) : c =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["b"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3 * a) * (-3 * a) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["9a²", "9a^2"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "a/(3a) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["1/3"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a/b) : (c/d) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["ad/(bc)", "(ad)/(bc)", "ad/bc"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "7^0 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["1"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "number"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + b) : c =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["(a+b)/c", "a/c + b/c"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5 * a * 3) : 3 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["5a"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "c * (a + b) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["ac+bc", "ca+cb", "bc+ac"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3 * a)^2 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["9a²", "9a^2"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3 + a) * (3 + a) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["a²+6a+9", "a^2+6a+9", "9+6a+a²"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7/3) * (2/5) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["-14/15"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + b)^2 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["a²+2ab+b²", "a^2+2ab+b^2"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "15a/a =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["15"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "number"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3b) : 3 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["a/3 + b", "(a+3b)/3", "a/3 + 3b/3"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a/b) : (c/d) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["ad/(bc)", "(ad)/(bc)", "ad/bc"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "10^3 * 10^2 * 10^1 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["1000000", "10^6"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a * 3b) : (-3) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["-ab"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 * 10^0 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["3"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "number"
  },
  {
    "question": "7/0 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["nem értelmezett", "0-val nem osztunk", "nincs értelmezve", "hiba"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a/b) * (c/d) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["ac/(bd)", "(ac)/(bd)", "ac/bd"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a * b)^2 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["a²b²", "a^2b^2"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + b + d) * c =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["ac+bc+dc", "ca+cb+cd"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7 + 2b)^2 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["49+28b+4b²", "49+28b+4b^2", "4b²+28b+49"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5 + a) : 3 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["(5+a)/3", "5/3 + a/3"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "3/5 - 2/7 =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["11/35"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2/7)a * (-7b) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["-2ab"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3/5)a + (2/7)b - (1/7)a =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["(16/35)a + (2/7)b", "16a/35 + 2b/7"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + b) * (a - b) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["a²-b²", "a^2-b^2"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a^3 * b^(-4))/(a^4 * b^(-5)) =",
    "type": "text",
    "answer": ["b/a", "b/a"],
    "points": 1,
    "match_type": "contains"
  }
]